♪♪～
Halharl Infigar!
（アラジン）「灼熱の双掌」！
♪♪～
What amazing power.
（ヤムライハ・心の声）≪すごい出力。→
His perverted tendencies are deceiving, but he really is a Magi.
エロガキのくせに
さすがは　マギね≫
はぁ～。　どうだい？　おねえさん。
How was that?
うん　全然ダメね。
えっ？
Absolutely terrible.
Your magoi output is certainly amazing.
確かに　魔力の出力はすごい。→
However, simply releasing a lot of heat is a bit too simple to be called magic.
けれど　ただの熱の放出で
魔法としては　単純ね。
What do you mean?
どういうことだい？
（ヤムライハ）魔法ってのはね→
Magic does a lot more.
もっと
いろんなことができるのよ。
For example, something like this.
例えば　こんなふうに。
あっ！　おねえさん？
Miss?
（ヤムライハ）ここよ。
あっ。
I'm here.
これは　「隠者の水膜」。
うわぁ～！
This is called Sharrar Magd.
水を集める　水蒸気に変換する→
It's done by giving the rukh three commands.
Gather water, change the water into vapor, and manipulate the refraction of light.
光を屈折させる
という３つの命令式を→
ルフに与えているの。
命令式？
Commands?
（ヤムライハ）魔法とはね　術式なのよ。
Magic is made of formulas.
What commands you give the rukh
determine exactly what actions will occur.
どのような命令を
ルフに与えれば→
何が起こるかは
はっきり決まっている。→
This is the invisible truth that governs our world.
それは　この世を構成している
見えない真理だわ。→
To understand these formulas, to put them together, and therefore to give rise to different phenomenon,
それを解き明かし　組み合わせ
さまざまな現象を引き起こす→
is magic.
それこそが魔法よ。→
Someone who can use as much magoi as yourself might be able to combine hundreds of commands
君ほどの魔力の使い手なら
修行しだいで→
and perform great magics, but it all
depends on how much training you undergo.
何百もの命令式を組み合わせた
大魔法だって使えるかもしれない。
♪♪～
I understand now.
そうか　魔法とは
そういうものだったんだね。
So that's magic.
ふふっ。
ありがとう　おねえさん。
Thanks, miss.
Please teach me lots more about magic!
その魔法を
もっともっと僕に教えておくれよ。
（アリババ）はあ～！
（シャルルカン）はい！
ぐわっ！　痛ぇ～…。
You've got openings all over.
（シャルルカン）がら空きだなぁ。　お前
ほんとに　その剣でやるのか？
Are you sure about using that sword?
んん…。　俺の魔装→
My Djinn Equip blade is around this size, so I really want to master this.
こういう感じなんで→
これで　なんとかしたいんです。
（シャルルカン）つっても　お前の剣
折れて　炎も出ねぇんだろ？
But isn't your sword broken to the point where it doesn't even shoot out flames anymore?
It... is.
それは　そうなんですけど…。
≪あれ以来　アモンは
まったく応えてくれない≫
Ever since I broke it, Amon hasn't responded to me at all.
That does look pretty bad.
（シンドバッド）確かに　ひどい状態だな。
Sinbad!
シンドバッドさん。
We've got to do something about that knife.
（シンドバッド）まずは
その剣を　なんとかしないとな。
えっ？
（シンドバッド）来たまえ。
Come with me.
ガチャ（扉の音）
（シンドバッド）その剣は→
That knife's no good anymore.
もうダメだろう。
えっ!?
What?
It's not like your djinn is dead.
（シンドバッド）
ジンが　死んだのではない。→
I mean that if you transfer your djinn to another metal vessel, you'll be able to use him again.
ほかの金属器に
ジンを移し替えれば→
また使えるようになる。
Thank goodness.
よかった。
（シンドバッド）しかし　なんの金属に→
But the problem is what metal vessel to transfer him to.
移し替えるかが問題だな。
（２人）えっ？
Djinn manifest their power by becoming one with their masters.
（シンドバッド）ジンとは　主と一体化して
力を発揮するもの。→
As such, metal vessels should be items that their masters have worn for a long time,
故に　その金属器は→
長い間　身に付けたものか→
or items that their masters have strong emotional attachments to.
思い入れや
縁のあるものが望ましい。→
そのナイフも
大切なものだったんだろ？
Your knife fits that description, doesn't it?
It's not really all that impressive.
そんな
大したものじゃないんですが→
王宮入りして間もない頃→
A little while after I entered the palace,
during my practical economy lessons, the former king of Balbadd, my dad, came to see me just once.
商学の課外実習を　バルバッド先王…→
父が
一度だけ　見に来たことがあって→
That day was the first time I succeeded in a trade negotiation,
俺は
その日　初めて交渉に成功して→
and I bought this knife with the profits.
そのもうけで
手に入れたナイフなんです。
It was actually pretty cheap.
いや…　安物なんですけどね。
But I'm kind of sad it's broken.
壊れて　ちょっと残念です。
（シンドバッド）なるほど
先王に　ゆかりのあるナイフか。
I understand. That knife is a connection to the late king.
これは？
（シンドバッド）俺が昔→
What's this?
This is a sword the late king gifted to me a while ago.
バルバッド先王から授かった剣だ。
あっ…　父から？
That's from my dad?
There was a battle in which I had hurt both my people and my country, and I was feeling lost and confused.
（シンドバッド）
とある戦で　国と民が傷つき→
道に迷っていた俺にくれたものだ。
He gave me this sword then and told me to have strength.
心を引き締めよ…　とな。
♪♪～
Now, I will pass it onto you.
（シンドバッド）今度は　俺が　君に託そう。
If you wish to once again take up a blade,
もし君に　再び　剣を取り→
if there is something you must do, it is yours.
志さねばならぬものがあるのなら。
♪♪～
命を懸けて。
I stake my on life on it.
♪♪～
あっ。
ああっ！
アモンが移った。
Amon transferred!
Your djinn transferred over so quickly. I'm sure your father's guiding you.
（シンドバッド）
こんなにすぐ　ジンが移るなんて→
お父上の導きかもしれないな。
あっ。
♪♪～
miwatasu kagiri no kouya ni hitori tatteirunda
In the wilderness, as far as the eye can see, stands a lone figure
sorya miburui mo surun darou
Surely he trembles as he stands
♪♪～
osanai shoujo ga yume ni miteiru hakuba no ouji mitaina mono
A young girl dreams of a prince on a white horse
♪♪～
bokura mo dokka de shiranai uchi ni kitai shiteshimatteitano kamo
Unwittingly, we also fall to such dreams of perfection
fukanzen na kono sekai wo dareka ga
No one will recreate
♪♪～
kakitashite kureru nante nai
this imperfect world for us
♪♪～
shinjiru toiu kotoba wo kimi ha kodomoppoi to warau kai?
Will you call me naïve if I say that I still dream?
miwatasu kagiri no kouya de yukisaki wo shimesu mono
In the wilderness, as far as the eye can see, shines a guiding light
♪♪～
mune ni daite aruitekou sekai ga hohoemu
Hold it close as you go and the world will smile upon you
kono basho ga doko darou to miagereba mabataku hoshi
If you're lost, consult the twinkling stars
♪♪～
sono shita de kimi wo omoeba warukunai yoru ni naru
If I think of you while gazing at those stars, the night brightens
tsumetai mune ni hi ga tomoru
and a warm fire lights in my heart
19th Night
The Star's Name is Sinbad
Now it's Morgiana's turn.
（シンドバッド）さて　次は　モルジアナの番だ。
（モルジアナ）えっ？
What?
（シンドバッド）この中から
好きな金属の品を１つ選びなさい。
Pick any metal item that you like from this room.
（２人）えっ。
わ…　私がですか？
Are you talking to me?
Yes.
（シンドバッド）
うん。　君が　アリババ君たちと→
If you plan on fighting alongside Alibaba and
Aladdin, you could become part of their household.
共に戦うのなら
その眷族になる場合がある。
（２人）あっ。
眷族？
Household?
Household refers to the warriors who support a King Candidate.
王の器にひかれ　王の魔力と→
They receive magoi from him and a blessing of power from his djinn to fight alongside of him.
そのジンの能力の恩恵を受ける→
強力な戦士だ。
あっ。
In order for that to happen, you need to have a
vessel to hold that power, or a household vessel.
（シンドバッド）
そのためには　眷属器と呼ばれる→
力を宿す器が　必要なのだよ。→
As long as it's metal and it touches your body, anything will work.
身に付ける金属なら
なんでもいい。→
Any of these would look beautiful on you, Morgiana.
モルジアナなら
どれも　よく似合うよ。
あっ…。　そんなもの→
I-I've never worn anything in here before.
どれも
身に付けたことがありません。
≪おっ　モルジアナ！
（２人）ん？
Wow, Morgiana!
This would look great on you, don't you think?
これなんか　似合うんじゃねぇか？
Alibaba... that's not something you say to a girl!
≪アリババ君
女の子に　それはないだろう…≫
Do they look good on me?
私に似合いますか？
うん！　すっげぇ強そう。
You look really strong!
What? Does she actually look happy?
（シンドバッド）≪あれ？
なんか　うれしそうだぞ≫
To be honest, some metal piece that
you've had for a long time is also best.
まあ　本当は　モルジアナも→
ずっと身に付けていた金属の方が
いいんだが。
えっ？　んん…。
あっ。　あの…→
Anything works as long as it's metal, right?
金属なら　なんでもいいんですか？
（シンドバッド）ああ。
Yes.
（２人）あっ。
おい　これって…。
Wait, aren't those...
はい　私が
ずっと付けていた足かせです。
Yes, these are the shackles I used to wear.
I couldn't throw them away, so I kept
bringing them with me everywhere I went.
捨てられずに
ずっと持っていました。
This was something Aladdin used to encourage me,
これは　アラジンが語りかけ→
something Goltas broke for me,
ゴルタスが断ち切り→
and something you freed me from, Alibaba.
アリババさんが外してくれた→
私の大切な人たちからの
恩義の積もった→
This is something I'm proud of, filled with all of the support of those most important to me.
誇らしい大事な品です。
（２人）ふっ。
≪コツ　コツ　コツ　コツ（足音）
Master Sin.
≪（ジャーファル）シン様。
（３人）ん？
（ジャーファル）煌帝国の使節団が
ご到着されました。
The delegation from the Kou Empire has arrived.
♪♪～
Kou
（アリババ　アラジン）あっ。
So he's the Kou Empire's prince.
≪彼が　煌帝国の皇子か≫
（イスナーンの声）憎め。
Hate him.
≪なんだ？≫
What was that?
（白龍）煌帝国第四皇子→
I am the fourth prince of the Kou Empire, Hakuryuu Ren.
練白龍です。
（シンドバッド）陛下から伺っている。→
I have heard of you from His Majesty.
歓迎するよ。
（白龍）義父の命でなくとも→
I welcome you.
Even without my father-in-laws orders, I wished to visit you.
貴殿には
お会いしたいと思っておりました。
I am honored to hear that.
（シンドバッド）
それは光栄だ。　ところで→
But who is the person standing behind you, Prince Hakuryuu?
白龍殿の後ろの貴人は…。
（ジャーファル）ああ～！
Princess K-Kougyoku Ren!
（ジャーファル）れ…　練紅玉殿！
（ヒナホホ）ああ～　シンドバッドに
気があるってヤツか。
Is she interested in Sinbad?
She followed him all the way out here!
（ピスティ）追っかけてきたんだぁ。
うふっ！
Yeah!
Thank you for last time.
（紅玉）先日はどうも。
またお会いできて　うれしいわ。
I'm so happy to be able to see you again.
（シンドバッド）こちらこそ。
（ジャーファル）えっ？
I am as well.
What?
Aw, she's talking to him normally.
（ピスティ）あれ？　普通だよ？
（ジャーファル）よかった…→
Thank goodness.
It seems like nothing happened between them.
何もないみたいだ。
（シャルルカン）えっ？　な～んだぁ。
Oh, seriously?
お久しぶりですね。　煌帝国では→
It's been a while!
I didn't see you at all when I visited the Kou Empire...
一度も　お会いする機会が
ありませんでしたね。→
いや～　また会えて
本当によかった。　はははっ！
It's a pleasure to see you again now!
You didn't see me, huh?
（紅玉）会う機会が
一度もなかったですって？
えっ？
（紅玉）ふん！
（ジャーファル）ああ～！
（ピスティ）ああっ！
What?
えっ？
（紅玉）シンドバッドめ…→
Damn you, Sinbad!
謝ったら　国のため　涙を飲んで
耐え忍ぼうと思ったけど→
If you had apologized, I was going to try to swallow my tears and deal with it for the sake of my country!
But I can't let you get away with this!
やっぱり許せないわ！
I challenge you to a duel, Sinbad!
決闘しなさい　シンドバッド！
You deserve nothing but death for disgracing a maiden's body with such barbarianism!
乙女の身を辱めた蛮行
万死に値する!!
（一同）えっ!?
（ジャーファル）やっぱり～！→
I knew it!
な…　何したんですか!?
（シンドバッド）えっ!?　何もしてないよ！
What did you do?
I-I didn't do anything!
（ジャーファル）
どういうことなんですか!?　姫！
What do you mean?
Princess!
あっ…。　ううっ…。→
うぅ…　ああ～…。
（ジャーファル）あっ！
（紅玉）ううっ…。
（ヒナホホ）泣かしちまったじゃねぇか。
（ジャーファル）あっ…　えっと　その…。
（夏黄文）失礼。
Pardon me.
これ以上
本人の口から告げさせるのは→
It would be considered cruel and unusual to force the victim to say anymore.
酷というもの。
私に　続けさせてください。
Please allow me to explain in her place.
（夏黄文）本人の話によれば
次のとおりです。
The princess' tale goes such.
（回想）((ははははっ))
It was the last night of King Sinbad's visit to the Kou Empire.
（夏黄文）シンドバッド王の
煌帝国ご滞在　最後の夜→
A lavish farewell banquet was held.
別れの酒宴が催されました。→
The next morning, Princess Kougyoku awoke in bed to see...
その夜が明け
寝床で　紅玉姫が目覚めると…。
((ん？))
((はっ！))
（ジャーファル）ああ～…。
（夏黄文）これで→
If you insist that there was nothing,
please do explain how that happened!
何もなかったというのなら…。
（紅玉）うう～～…。
是非とも　ご説明頂きたく→
King Sinbad!
シンドバッド王！
えっ…　えっ？　あっ…。
（紅玉）ううっ！　うぅ…。
I am Sinbad, King of Sindria.
（シンドバッド）≪私は
シンドリア国王　シンドバッド。→
I have overcome many difficulties in my life,
幾多の苦難を
乗り越えてきた私だが→
今　かつてない危機に
直面している≫
but I've never dealt with anything like this before.
くっ！　煌帝国皇女の身を汚した
シンドバッドめ！→
You've disgraced the body of a
princess of the Kou Empire, Sinbad!
私と　決闘しなさい！
I'll duel you to defend my honor!
If you refuse, I'll kill you, then kill myself!
断れば
あなたを殺して　私も死ぬ～…。
おお～…　おいたわしや　姫！→
Do-Don't be hasty, Princess!
What a distressing situation!
なんたる大事態！
（従者）収めてください！
Don't let her hurt herself!
≪俺が致したのか？≫
Did I do that?
This is going to sound bad, but I
really can't remember anything at all.
≪悪いが　まったく記憶がない≫
"The High King of the Seven Seas has never lost himself to
alcohol and done something inappropriate with a woman..."
≪七海の覇王ともあろう男が→
酒に溺れ　女性に粗相するなど…≫
...is not something that I can say.
≪今まで
なかったとは言わないが≫
The obscenities of the King of Sindria
（ジャーファル）シンドリア国王の淫行。
（シンドバッド）あっ…。
and the suicide of a princess
（ジャーファル）そして　皇女の自害。
（シンドバッド）うっ！
all lead to a war with the Kou Empire!
（ジャーファル）更に　煌帝国との戦争へ！
（シンドバッド）ああっ！
（シンドバッド）
≪そ…　そのような国民への不義→
I-I would never allow such injustice to befall my people!
俺は　断じて犯さん！≫
Wait a sec. Why is this happening?
≪待て待て。　そもそも　一体
なぜ　こんなことになったのだ？≫
The whole time I was at the palace, I never even saw her once!
≪俺は　滞在中
彼女と　一度も会ってすらいない≫
Wait, that night, the King wasn't drunk at all!
（シャルルカン）そういえば　あの夜
王様は　全然酔ってなかったぜ。
Yeah.
（スパルトス）ああ。
（シンドバッド）だろう!?
Right?
（シンドバッド）((ははははっ))
（シンドバッド）酒は
儀礼として　ひとふた口だけ。→
I only had a few sips out of courtesy.
And after that, I went straight to my bedroom.
そのあと
俺は　まっすぐ寝所へ戻った。
We made sure of that.
（スパルトス）
それは　私たちが　しかと見届けた。
Exactly! I went straight to bed!
そう！　俺は　そのまま眠ったのだ。
I didn't do anything with the princess!
やはり
姫君とは　何もなかったのだ。
Then why was I in your room?
では　なぜ
私が　あなたの部屋にいたの!?
（シンドバッド）うっ！　姫君→
I'm really sorry, Princess, but I have no memories of that.
どうも
私には　その記憶がないのだが…。
Then why were you naked?
じゃあ
なぜ　あなたは裸だったの!?
Did you strip off your clothes while you were sleeping?!
寝ている間に
服を脱ぎ捨てることがあって!?
Yes.
（シンドバッド）
うん　それは　よくあることだ。
I do that quite often.
（紅玉）ふん！　ふざけないで！
あっ…。
Stop lying!
If you really plan on playing innocent, I'll tell you my side of the story!
そこまで
しらを切るつもりなら→
今度は　私の言い分を
聞いていただこうかしら！→
That night, I hid myself in a corner of the banquet room.
あの夜　私は　宴の片隅にいたわ。→
でも　結局
声を掛けることもできぬまま→
But I could never muster up the courage to speak to you.
But I could never muster up the courage to speak to you. The banquet ended.
宴は終わった。→
そして　そのあと→
After that,
I was attacked by something, lost consciousness,
私は　何者かに襲われ意識を失い→
and awoke to find myself in your room, Sinbad!
気付けば
私は　シンドバッド様のお部屋で→
朝を迎えていたわ。
（紅玉）((きゃあ～～!!))
（一同）あぁ…。
（ジャーファル）それは　つまり？
In other words-
（夏黄文）つまり
こういうことでありましょう！
In other words, THIS happened!
あ～ははははっ！
はははっ…　はっ！
うっ！
In order to satisfy your own twisted lust, you went so far as to knock the princess unconscious
（夏黄文）
己のゆがんだ欲望を満たさんと→
姫君を昏倒させたうえ→
before proceeding to commit your crime!
行為に及んだのでありましょう。
（ヤムライハ　ピスティ）きゃあ～！
（ジャーファル）最低ですね。
How terrible!
（シンドバッド）
お前ら信じろよ　自分の王を！→
You guys! Believe in your king!
ったく…。　俺が　外交の最中に
酒で失態を犯すなど→
Come on, do you guys really think I would get drunk and commit a crime while on a diplomatic mission?
お前たちは　本当だと思うか!?
（一同）んん～…。
（シンドバッド）あっ。
We do.
（ジャーファル）
思います。　酒癖においては→
We have no faith in you when you're drunk.
まったく信用しておりません。
（マスルール）毎度のことっすから。
Cause this happens every time.
（スパルトス）手を出されたという
女性からの苦情が絶えません。
The complaints from girls you've slighted is never-ending.
（ピスティ）こないだなんて
すっごいおばあちゃんだったよね。
There was even an old grandmother who complained recently!
（ヒナホホ）未然に防いだけどな。
（ヤムライハ）実は私も→
She was able to defend herself before it happened though.
You even made a move on me once.
一度　手を…。
（シャルルカン）なっ…→
What did you say?
んだと～!?
お前たち…。→
You guys...
All of you are my trusted subordinates.
だれもかれも
旅の中で出会い　共に冒険し→
We met on my travels, had adventures
together, and built a trust for one another.
信頼を築き上げた
部下たちなのに→
What happened to that?
それが　どうだ。→
Masrur was once a gladiator slave
who looked at me with dead eyes.
マスルールは
剣奴をしていた頃の→
絶望と諦めの目で俺を見ている。→
ジャーファルなど
出会った当初の→
When I first met Jafar, he glared at me through the eyes of an assassin.
暗殺者の目で　俺を見やがる。
♪♪～
（シンドバッド）なんだよ…。→
What is this...
お…　俺たちの信頼関係は
うそだったのかよ!?
Is the trust we placed in one another and the bonds we formed nothing more than lies?!
As if we'd listen to the words of a drunkard!
（ジャーファル）酔っ払いの言うことを
いちいち聞いてられるか！
（ピスティ）ふだんは
いい王様なんだけどね。
He's normally a good king though.
In order for you to take responsibility for
your actions, you must marry the princess!
（夏黄文）責任を取るには
姫君と結婚するほかありません。
（シンドバッド）なっ！　結婚だと!?
Marry?
うっ　ううっ…。
そうでありましょう！
Yes!
夫婦の契りがあったとすれば
姫の名誉は傷つかぬ。
If you are husband and wife, then the princess' honor will remain intact!
我が皇帝陛下も　あなた様なら
姫を差し出すでしょう。
His Majesty, the Kou Emperor, would
surely give you the princess' hand in marriage.
（シンドバッド）ちょ…　ちょっと待て。→
W-Wait a moment!
I haven't agreed to anything yet.
何を勝手に…。
（ジャーファル）致し方なし。
We have no other way.
（ヤムライハ）煌帝国と政略結婚など…。
A political marriage with the Kou?
（ジャーファル）戦争か友好かでは
選択の余地はなかろう。
We only have two choices: war or friendship.
That's really no choice at all.
（ヒナホホ）しかたない。
（ドラコーン）主の失態と→
It is a retainer's duty to deal with his master's faults...
運命を共にするのも…。
（マスルール）臣下の務めっすからね。
...and accompany him wherever his path leads.
King Sinbad, your decision.
（ジャーファル）シンドバッド王　ご決断を。
♪♪～
（シンドバッド）
ああ～～!!　もう我慢ならん！
I can't take this anymore!
ヤムライハ　お前の力で
俺の無実を証明してくれ。
Yamraiha, use your power to prove my innocence!
いいんですか？
私は　本当にあったことしか→
Are you sure?
I can only show exactly what happened.
見せることができませんよ？
かまわん！
That's fine!
Then please gather around.
（ヤムライハ）では来てください。
（シンドバッド）んん…。
Princess, you too.
（ヤムライハ）皇女様　あなたも。
（紅玉）あっ。
（ヤムライハ）見せてあげる
本当は　何があったのか。
I'll show you what really happened.
ああっ！　いけません　姫君！
You must not, Princess!
（ヤムライハ）「真実の水人形劇」！
Sharrar Raqesa!
これは一体…。
What is this?
We'll have their rukh show us what happened that night.
（ヤムライハ）二人のルフに　事件の
夜のことを語ってもらうの。→
この魔法に　うそはつけないわよ。
This magic shows only the truth!
あっ！
（ヤムライハ）寝てるわね。→
He's sleeping.
姫様は？
（紅玉）んん…。
What about the princess?
歩いてる。
（一同）あっ！
She's walking.
（シャルルカン）おお…。
浮いた。
She's floating!
Someone's carrying her.
（ヤムライハ）誰かに　運ばれてるのね。→
And they put her to sleep right next to King Sinbad.
そして　シンドバッド王の隣へ
寝かされた…　と。
Then Mister Sinbad didn't do anything after all.
じゃあ　おじさんは
何もしてなかったんだね。
（ヤムライハ）んん…。　これからかもよ。
Keep watching!
（シャルルカン）
誰かに　運ばせたのかもしれねぇ。
He might've had someone carry her for him!
（ジャーファル）
子供は見てはいけません！
Children should not watch!
（スパルトス）でも
私たちには　見届ける義務がある。
But we have a duty to stand witness.
（ヒナホホ）そう！
（ピスティ）いや～ん！
♪♪～
I'm going to fast forward.
（ヤムライハ）早回しするわね。
((コケコッコー！（鳥の鳴き声）))
朝だ。
It's morning.
They only slept.
（ピスティ）寝てるだけだよ？
（シンドバッド）おお～！
（一同）あっ。
So nothing happened.
（ジャーファル）結局　何も…。
（シンドバッド）ほら見ろ！→
I told you so!
I didn't do anything!
俺は　何もやってねぇだろ！
（一同）ああっ…。
あぁ…　あっ！
（シンドバッド）ったく…→
Seriously, do you know how betrayed I felt?
俺が
どれだけ悲しい気持ちになったか。
（夏黄文）ああ～…。
（シンドバッド）姫！
We're sorry.
Princess!
As you just witnessed, nothing happened.
ご覧のとおり　何もなかった。
Both your body and your honor are uninjured!
あなたの身も名誉も
傷ついていないのです。
（紅玉）そ…　そうですね…。
I-I see...
You must not be fooled!
（夏黄文）
だまされてはなりません！→
Such suspicious magic does not serve as proof!
そんな怪しい魔法など
証明になりません。→
潔く　罪を認めなさい
シンドバッド王！
Be a man and acknowledge your sins, King Sinbad!
（紅玉）もうやめて　夏黄文！
（夏黄文）はっ！→
Stop it, Ka Koubun!
Princess!
姫君…。
本当は　自分でも→
I thought it was kind of strange, honestly.
おかしいと思ってたの。
服も髪も　乱れてなかったし…。
でも　訳が分からなくて→
Neither my hair nor my clothes were in any disarray.
But I just couldn't understand...
怖くて騒いでしまって…。
（夏黄文）ああっ。
I was scared and I caused a lot of trouble...
（紅玉）ごめんなさい。
（一同）あっ。
I'm sorry!
（夏黄文）あぁ…。
姫君！
Princess!
姫君　なんと…。
（ヤムライハ）な…　なんか→
Oh Princess!
I-I feel bad for her.
かわいそうなことに
なっちゃったわね。
But doesn't that mean the culprit is still out there?
（シャルルカン）しかしよぉ…　ってことは
犯人は　別にいるってことだ。
（ヤムライハ）こんな悪質なことを…。
What a horrible thing to do...
But who did it?
（ジャーファル）一体　誰が？
Princess!
姫…。
姫君。
Princess...
≪私の名は　夏黄文≫
My name is Ka Koubun.
I am Princess Kougyoku's attendant.
≪紅玉姫の従者である。→
My princess, whom I have long served, has been put
through a distressing situation thanks to a certain someone.
長年　お仕えした大切な姫君が
何者かによって→
このような目に
遭わされているわけだが…≫
≪ちなみに　犯人は私である。→
And that someone was me.
That night, I made the princess fall unconscious,
あの夜　私は　姫君を気絶させ→
and, with the help of her two other
attendants, brought her to King Sinbad's bed.
従者二人と　シンドバッド王の→
寝所へ届けたのである。→
Why did I do such a thing?
そもそも　なぜ　私が
このような行動に出たのか。→
I had a plan.
私には　計画があった。→
I was going to accompany the princess on her political marriage to the King of Balbadd,
バルバッドに嫁ぐ姫に　付き従い→
Baby
やがて
生まれる世継ぎの後見人として→
become the guardian of their child,
and control the country from the shadows.
国を操る計画だ。→
Baby
But things did not go as planned.
しかし　それは頓挫してしまった≫
≪だが　そこへ現れたのが
シンドバッド王だ。→
And there appeared King Sinbad.
I would make what failed in Balbadd succeed in Sindria!
バルバッドの代わりに
シンドリアでそれを成し遂げる。→
And the princess could marry the man of her dreams!
姫君とて
意中の男と夫婦になれる。→
Two birds with one stone!
まさに　一石二鳥！→
That magic thingiejig revealed the truth,
魔法とやらで
真相が　バレそうになったが→
強気でいけば
押し切れそうな雰囲気だ≫
but this still feels like a situation that can be controlled with a bit of persistence!
You mustn't be taken in by them, Princess!
（夏黄文）丸め込まれては
なりませんぞ　姫君！
You must have King Sinbad take responsibility and marry you!
シンドバッド王に　責任を取って
結婚していただくのであります！
I will force my way through this!
≪今回こそ
ゴリ押ししてくれるわ！≫
I am so sorry!
（従者）申し訳ありません！
えっ？
Everything was orchestrated by Sir Ka Koubun.
全部　夏黄文さんがやりました。
私たちが手伝いました。
And we assisted him!
（紅玉）えっ？
（夏黄文）何ぃ～!?→
A-A-Are you guys stupid?
バ　バ…　バカか　お前ら！
（従者）だって→
But don't you feel bad for the princess?
姫君　かわいそうだし。
（ジャーファル）シンドバッド王を陥れた→
Capture the traitor who tried to deceive King Sinbad!
反逆者をひっ捕らえろ！
（夏黄文）くぅ～！
ここで捕まるわけにはいかん！
（一同）ああっ！
I will not be captured here!
バシ！
（夏黄文）ううっ！
（ジャーファル）白龍皇子。
（白龍）もう茶番はいいでしょう。
Prince Hakuryuu!
Stop this farce.
（一同）あっ…。
（白龍）シンドバッド王よ→
King Sinbad, this issue was the fault of my country's misconduct.
今度の騒動
我が国の者の不義です。
（一同）あっ！
（夏黄文）ああっ…。
（白龍）
我が国にも　透視魔法はある。→
Clairvoyance magic also exists in my country.
あの水魔法も正しいと見た。→
I believe that water magic showed the truth.
Am I wrong, Ka Koubun?
違うか？　夏黄文。
（夏黄文）あっ！　はい…。
No.
（白龍）
同行者の非礼　煌帝国を代表して→
As the representative of the Kou Empire, I offer my sincerest apologies for the misconduct of my fellow travelers.
お詫び申し上げる。
（シンドバッド）あっ…。
ですが
今回の留学　目的は別にあるゆえ→
As the purpose of this trip is unrelated to this
incident, I beg of you to please permit us to stay.
どうか
滞在を　お許しいただきたい。
（シンドバッド）ああ。　許可しよう。
（白龍）ありがとうございます。
Of course, permitted.
Thank you very much.
What a stupid thing to do.
こんなくだらないことで…。
（夏黄文）えっ！
皇子に　膝を折らせるなんて。
（夏黄文）くだらなくない！→
Our poor prince had to bow down and apologize...
It wasn't stupid!
しかたなかったんだよ…。→
I had no choice!
僕みたいな汚らわしいクズが
夢を見るには→
For lowly trash like me to fulfill my
dreams, I had no choice but to do this!
こうするしかなかったんだよ～！
Don't say that!
（紅玉）そんなこと言わないで！
（夏黄文）あっ！
You're a great person, Ka Koubun.
夏黄文は　立派ないい子よ。
はっ！
姫君…　うわぁ～～！　ううっ…。
Princess!
ああ～！　うぅ…。
And that situation felt like one where an apology would win me forgiveness.
≪謝れば
許していただけそうな雰囲気≫
≪ここは　力のかぎり
謝っておくであります≫
If so, then I'll apologize until my face is blue!
（夏黄文）あっ。
ぺっ！
（夏黄文）う…　うわっ！
（ジャーファル）
いいんですか？　彼らを許して。
Was it okay to let them go?
Yeah. His Highness, the prince, did not seem like he'd go home with his mission unfulfilled.
（シンドバッド）いいさ。
少なくとも　あの皇子殿下は→
目的とやらを果たすまでは
帰ってくれそうもないからな。
It's amazing.
（白龍）すばらしい。→
You built this empire in just one generation,
一代にして
これほどの王国を築かれ→
and brought together the powerful Seven Seas Alliance.
強力な七海連合も
束ねておられる。→
It must have taken extraordinary skill and
magnanimity on your part to do such a thing.
なみなみならぬ才覚と
仁徳のなせる業なのでしょうね。
You exaggerate.
大げさだな　君は。
いえ。
No. You were the first to ever speak so forcefully to the Emperor of Kou.
煌の皇帝に　あんなに強く
物を言ってのけたのは→
貴殿が　初めてなのですよ。
I was just wholeheartedly focused on
stopping the weapons pointed at Balbadd.
それは　バルバッドへの矛を
収めてもらいたい→
一心だったからだ。
I wish to continue friendly relations with the Kou Empire.
煌帝国と
友好的な関係を続けたいのだよ。
King Sinbad.
（白龍）シンドバッド王よ。
ん？
Yes?
あなたは　うそをついている。
You are lying.
♪♪～
Friendly relations are but a superficial pretense.
友好関係など
表面上のものでしょう？
What are you trying to say?
一体　何が言いたいのかな？
Please don't misunderstand.
誤解しないでください。
私は　別に→
My goal is not to become enemies with you at all.
あなたと
敵対したいわけではありません。
I have important information to share.
重要な知らせがあるのです。
ん？
The organization that's currently dwelling in the shadows of Kou is targeting Sindria.
煌帝国に巣くう組織が
シンドリアを狙っています。
They have already started to act.
それは　すでに動きだしている。
If that's true, why would a prince of the Kou Empire such as yourself come and tell me?
それが真実だとして→
煌帝国の皇子である君が
なぜ私に？
What is your goal?
君の目的は　一体　なんだ？
煌帝国を滅ぼすことです。
To destroy the Kou Empire.
♪♪～
"kimi ni ha yuuki ga aru"
"You're a hero."
sono hitokoto wo shinji tobidashita
Off you went, believing in those words
mawari ha kare wo waratte
While those around you mocked you
♪♪～
"douse nani hitotsu aitsu ni ha dekinai sa"
"Let him go. He can't do anything."
iwaseteoke
Let them talk
kimi ha keshite yowaku nanka nai
You're far from weak
dare ni mo hatasenakatta yume wo negae tsuyoku
Believe in those dreams no one else could reach!
♪♪～
dare ni mo hatasenakatta yume wo negae tsuyoku
Believe in those dreams no one else could reach!
kanarazu kanaete miserutte
You'll definitely make them come true
♪♪～
saa mizukara no hata kakage
Come, fly your own flag
susume mae ni
and keep moving forward
nijimu namida ha
The tears you shed
kimi no akashi
are proof that you're alive
♪♪～
chikara ni narou
Draw strength from your tears!
mayou toki ha kono boku ga soba ni iru
When you are in trouble, I will be by your side
dakara ikou
So go!
♪♪～
sekai no subete wo mi ni
And see the world
Hakuryuu, you must gain knowledge.
Prince Alibaba, hate, kill.
Please allow me to join the Zagan party.
Next time: The Two Princes
20th Night
The Two Princes
The story takes us to a dungeon again.
静岡県浜松市のＪＲの工場で
去年発見された不発弾が
今日、爆破処理された。
市街地から海岸へ運んでの作業で
住民およそ１万人に避難指示が出
たほか、